Art Collins Collection ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series I: Iggy Pop Legal Papers, 1995-2004 and undated
  - "The Passenger" EMI Korea (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Warner Chappel / Bug Argentina, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Miami Vice Buyout 1998 home video (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - "Louie Louie" Kellogg's Spain (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Monster Man TV Ad / French restaurant (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - "Lust for Life" Best car video UK (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Fashion TV / "Live/Passenger" Canada license (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - SLC Punk / movie license (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - "Lust for Life" Top Gear Anthems (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - "China Girl" Disney (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - "The Passenger" The Adventures of Sebastian Cole (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - MTV Biorhythm (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - "Nightclubbing" MTV Legends (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - "Lust for Life" MCPS Education Video (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Michael Conte book release (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - "Search and Destroy" APC clothing (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - MTV Influences 11 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - IBM renewal, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Call sheets (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Pearl Jam contract (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Call sheets (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Iggy Pop Elvis tribute (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Whatever movie (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Bug Music statements, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Candy" Kilk Films (Greece) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "The Passenger" Whipped (Film) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Goran Bregovic songbook (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "Candy" The 90's Complete (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Success" Banana Republic (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Lust for Life/ The Passenger" Best Anthems Ever (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "Lust for Life" Millenium Movies (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Lust for Life" Mitsubishi TV (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Real Wild Child" Rock Comp. Germany (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Corruption" Be Rock Comp.(Greece) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Brick by Brick" Rockumentary (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Lust for Life" Steinlager Beer (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Korean Release (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - "The Passenger" Club Creatures (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - "The Passenger/Candy" ESSO (Latin America) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - "Nightclubbing" Oasis CD (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Eiffel Tower photograher (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Photographer promo cards (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - John Dittmar / Pinnacle Entertainment (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Aaron Jacoves correspondence (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "The Passenger" Kasbah Soundtrack (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Cry For Love" Time Life Vol. 13 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Avenue B record clubs (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Lust for Life" Most Naked Bands (VH1 Special) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "Shakin All Over" Drug awareness (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - "The Passenger" Digital Entertainment (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - "Search and Destroy" Orbiting Venus (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Nightclubbing" Oasis sample (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Goran Bregovic songbook CD (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Cold Metal" ESPN Olympics (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Real Wild Child" College Rock Compilation (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Death in Vegas correspondence (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Brent Hansen, President MTV (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - William Morris sample contract (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Virgin Records statements, January to June 1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - New album budget (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Bruce Weber / Let's Get Lost (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - “Corruption” video shoot (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Sessions at West 54th (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Avenue B press (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - New album travel (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Avenue B credits (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Avenue B advertisements (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - A&R / Keith Wood (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Iggy home pictures (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Bomp Records (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - New Milllenium Collections (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Versace / Connie Filippello (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Anthill T-Shirts (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Jim Travel (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - International promo (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Bug Music (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - "The Passenger" Doyle Film (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "Nightclubbing" Oasis sample (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Real Wild Child" Rock Autism demo (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Lust for Life" Royal Caribbean (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "It's Only Rock and Roll" Children's Promise (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - All Access Radio / MTV broadcast (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Miss Argentina" compilation (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - European Mid Priced: "Lust/Idiot" (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Living on the Edge of Night" GSA Countries (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Sixteen" LaPuce French films (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Real Wild Child" Venezula/Germany (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Recent Licensing, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "Passenger" Labatt's Blue (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "Lust for Life" EMI Scandanavia (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "Wild America" Platinum Rock 90's (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "China Girl" No Fun Pistols (Film) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Metallic KO / V2 Records (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Lust for Life" Sofinco (French Credit) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Soft Fruit / Photo Use (Australia) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Girl" Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - "The Passenger" Virgin Sweden (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Crispin Cioe / Burnzy Last Call (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Florida Concert / contracts (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "Lust for Life" This is Cult Fiction (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - "Real Wild Child" Mexico CD (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Missy Elliot sample (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Continental gig, April 1999 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - "Search and Destroy" Detroit Rock City (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Static Records / Pop OD CD (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - "Nightclubbing" Ange (French Film) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - "Passenger" Sony Music Norway (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - "Real Wild Child" Rock of the Century (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - "Passenger" Rock the Vote, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Recent Licensing Requests, April 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - "Lust for Life" Nokia Singapore (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - "Living on the Edge of Night' 90's Collection (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - "Search and Destroy" Erie Film (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - "Success" Banana Republic (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - "Living on the Edge of the Night" Wonderful 80's (Poland) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - "Lust for Life" FIFA 2000 The Album (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - "Lust for Life" Motivacation (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - "The Passenger" Virgin 25 Years (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - "Real Wild Child' Best Beer Songs (New Zealand) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - "Girls on NY" French Perfume (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - "Lust for Life"/"Born to Be Wild" Virgin UK (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - VH1 Behind the Music (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - SXSW 99 Iggy request (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Year 2525 / AK9 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - "Candy" Beauty Shop (Greece) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - "Lust for Life" Dressed in Black (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - "Social Life" Italian Insurance (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Pumping for Jill / Bug Music (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - "Lust for Life" LeColonne De Oscar (Italy) (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - "Lust for Life" Telstar/UK (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Mexico trip (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - "China Girl" Cupid/Bug (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - "Candy" Full Hits Rock (Venezuela) (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - "Lust for Life" Mail Order Japan (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Dan Rose / Wayne County Film (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - "Lust for Life" Bicentennial Man (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Linda Cohen / IFC In Your Ear (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - "Kill City" Charity sampler (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Nikki backyard designs (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - "Lust for Life" Power List (Scotland) (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - "Lust for Life” Transworld CD (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - "Lust for Life" LaFemme Nikita (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - "Candy" Benelux Top 10 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - "Lust for Life" Spiked! (Canada) (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - "Louie Louie" Sweden CD (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - "Highway Song" Baltic States CD (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - "Pumpin for Jill" Sweden (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - "Real Wild Child" Germany (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - "Funtime" VH1 Legends / Bowie (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - "Passenger" Barney Simon CD (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - "Passenger" DSB Denmark (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - "No Fun" Sex Pistols movie (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - "Passenger/Corruption" Pizza Hut (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - "Real Wild Child" Rock and Pop Moods (Netherlands) (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - "Real Wild Child" Rock and Pop Classics Volume 15 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - "Orbiting Venus/Master Charge" Bug Music (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - "The Passenger" Toyota UK 2000 option (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - "Lust for Life" Best of the 70's (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - "Lust for Life" Donn's Top 200 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Jazz on Cinema (Taiwan) (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - "The Passenger" Italian CD compilation (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - "The Passenger" Simply Best Drive (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - V2 Rhinoceros (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Caesar Poster/Cheese Fever movie (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - "Real Wild Child" A&M Portugal (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bust Magazine / reprint request (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Real Wild Child" A&M Australia (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Missy Elliot sample (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Candy Girl" Late Lunch (UK) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Pumpin for Jill" Commercial (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Lust for Life" Honda Civic (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bug Stooges Compositions / Warner (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Nude and Rude midpriced campaign (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - John Reese management (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Mark Romanek book (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Motorhead Tribute CD (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Mark Seliger photography (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Yanky Pankie UK show (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "I Wanna Live" Chevy Camaro (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - "Real Wild Child" Portugal compilation (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - "Lust for Life" Ally McBeal special (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - "Search and Destroy" Cameron Crowe film (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Goran Bregovic songbook (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - "Lust for Life" Procter and & Gamble (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - "Real Wild Child" A&M Australia (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - "The Passenger" Labatt's Blue (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Bicentennial Man / Virgin (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - "Real Wild Child" Time-Life Music (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - "Passenger/I Got a Right" Digital Entertainment (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - "Shake Appeal" All Cheerleaders Die (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "I Wanna Live" OOH La La (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Trivial Pursuit (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - High Fidelity Movie (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - HBO "Reverb" (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - The Mysterians (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - "Real Wild Child" Polygram Time Life Vol. 15 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" Rock Candy/Bug (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - "Lust for Life" EMI Korea (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Save the Children millennium gig (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Versace Men's Show Milan (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Virgin statement, June to December 1999 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" 20th Century Lullabies (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Canal / Belgium Tapings (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - MTV Euro Award letters, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - "Nightclubbing" Paris Canal Special (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Sig Sigworth memos (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Anthill merchandising (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - TMI/Grumble income, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Grumble Corporation, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - BMI royalty information (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Nick Tosches letter (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Principle Management / Dublin (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Call sheets, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Solo agency, Fall offers 1999 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - US promo (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Outstanding 1999 promo requests (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - V99 photographers lawsuit (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - MTV European Awards, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Britannica .com advertising (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Set list (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Promo posters (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Home to rent information (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Virgin license agreement, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Jewel Box Co. - Trainspotting CD (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Virgin/Gaumont battle (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Royalty contracts (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Snowday movie (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Revenge royalties (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Revenge royalties (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Royalty statements (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - MVO offers (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Grumble corporation (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Revenge/MCA records (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Don Was deal (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Revenge contract (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Virgin catalog contract (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - RCA contract (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Rosemary Carroll / Virgin license (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Virgin America delivery extension (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Solo offers, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Virgin Statement, January to June 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Lou Reed video (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Introduction to "Welcome to the Voice" (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Chief of police CD (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SXSW video (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cleopatra Records/Bug Music (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Lust for Life" - SFR Phones France (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Montreal Jazz Festival (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Corruption" Bug music (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Shaking All Over" ESPN Winter Games (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "The Passenger" Best Pub Jukebox Ever (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Lust for Life" Classical Love Songs in Hollywood (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "Lust for Life" IKEA CD (Sweden) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "The Passenger" The Big Spike (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "Lust for Life" Next Weekend's Party Album (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "Candy" FM Radio Anthems (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "Lust for Life" Cigarettes and Alcohol (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Buddah Records Re-Release (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - "Louie, Louie'' Lock, Stock TV soundtracks (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - "Lust for Life" Ralph's Best Songs Ever (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - "China Girl" The Real World (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - "Lust for Life" Ryan Caulfield TV Programs (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - "Johanna" Recycler film (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - "The Passenger" Limozeno (Bug Music) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Strictly Sinatra Covers/Cynthia Sexton (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - "Fucking Alone" Best Attitude Songs (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - "Real Wild Child" The Rock Collection (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - "The Passenger" Dommelsch Beer (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - "The Passenger" Champions of Rock (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - "Lust for Life" Shockwave San Jose Convention (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Poetry booklet (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - "Lust for Life" Corporate Video/Cingular Communication (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - "Nightclubbing/Bad Boys" Nash Bridges (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - "Lust for Life" All Time Movie Songs 2 (Canada) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - "I Need Somebody" Queer as Folk (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - "The Passenger" New World Disorder (Bug/Home Video) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1 The List (Bug Music) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - "Shake Appeal/Aiesha" VH1 Uses (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - "Corruption" O Music CD-R\release (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - "Avenue B" Gurten Festival (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Virgin Records Upper Mid Price, February 2000 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Mick Rock, 2000/09 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Mick Rock "Raw Power" Creation Books (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - "Real Wild Child" Universal Masters Collection (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - "The Passenger" Whipped Movie (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Jazz on Cinema (Singapore) (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - "Beside You" Mark Romanek DVD Release (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - "Lust for Life" Classic Rock 12 (Benelux) (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - "Lust for Life" Cheaters (HBO) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - "Aisha" computer game (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - "The Passenger" Best TV Ads (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - "Candy" Was Het Nu 70 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Erikson Tv Spot (UK) (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - "The Passenger" The Adventures of Sebastian Cole (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - "Search and Destroy" Karaoke CD France (Bug) (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - "Music to Watch Girls By" Millenia Nova (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - "Living on the Edge" Maxi Pop (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - "Lust for Life" Tucker (NBC) (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1 - The Go Go's (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - "The Passenger' Mountain Biking (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1 The List (Bug Music) (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - "The Passenger" Japanese Translation (EMI/Bug) (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Virgin Records catalog statement, July to December 2000 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Virgin Records current statement, July to December 2000 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - "Shaking All Over" Maybe Baby Movie (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - "Real Wild Child" Bad to the Bone CD (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Bedazzled Movie Caesar poster (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - "Lust for Life" Aprilia Motorcycles (Italy) (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - "Let Love Rule" Lenny Kravitz Virgin license (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - "Home" Parody lyrics (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Copyright renewals (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - "Beside You" Mark Romanek DVD release (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Bomp Records/Greg Shaw (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - "Tecknowledgy" Utah Saints Game use (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Steve Nieve Opera (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - "Corruption" Cheaters (Bug) (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - "The Passenger" Repsol/YPF (Argentina) (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - "The Passenger" Jaguar (Bug Music) (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - "The Passenger" Renault Clio (Italy) (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - "Lust for Life" Just Jeans (Australia) (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - "Da Mob" Script (Fox Television) (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - "Novocain" Five Foot One (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - "Felt the Luxury" MM&W Co-Write (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Bethlehem, PA date (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - "The Passenger" Experience Music (Project Seattle) (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Versace Milan (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Save the Last Dance Film / Heir Letters (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "Candy" Classic Rock 13 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You/Lover" Korea (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "Candy" Double Shot of Rock (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - "The Passenger" When Brenden Met Trudy (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Annie Lebowitz Pix / GQ Germany (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Bug Statement (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Sessions on West 54th / Bug Letter (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Leos Caras party (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Rolling Stone photo competition (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - William Morris demo / Tim Curtis (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - "The Passenger" New World Disorder (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - "I Need Somebody" KFC (UK and Erie) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - "Raw Power" VH1 1000 Greatest LPs (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - "In the Death Car" Hong Kong (Bug) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - "Lust for Life" Nissan (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Bad Boyz (HBO) IFC channel (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - "The Passenger" Panrico Bread (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - "The Passenger/Corruption" Pizza Hut (Australia) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - "The Passenger" Golden Age of Rock (Germany) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - "Real Wild Child" Rock Giants CD (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - "The Passenger" Sebastian Cole (Bug) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - "Spin Cycle/Dirt/I Got a Right" Bug (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Royal Caribbean, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Jazz Cinema Vol. 2 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - "Lust for Life" Ever Get the Feeling (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - "Lust for Life" Off The Top CD (Australia) (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - "Penetration" Intimacy (Sony) (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - "Lust for Life" Tucker (NBC) (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - "Nightclubbing" Modern Rock: Time Life (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - "Adami" French Money (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - "Real Wild Child" Biker Jens (Norway) (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - "Passenger" Robbie Williams DVD (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - "I Need Somebody" Queer as Folk (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1 Best Pump Up Song (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - "The Passenger" Jaguar Cars (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - "Façade" Angel Eyes (Movie) (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - "Raw Power" VH1 Legends / The Pretenders (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - "Search and Destroy" Shannon's Deal (NBC) (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - "Real Wild Child" On the Road Compilation (Sweden) (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - "Nightclubbing" The Source Sound Lab (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - "Aiesha" Evening Standard Ad (London) (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1 Behind the Music / The Go Go's (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - "Monster Men" Space Invaders Game (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - "Search and Destroy" Almost Famous Movie (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - "Raw Power" VH1 100 Greatest Albums of All Time (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - "The Passenger" Guinness commercial (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - "Lust for Life" VH1 Behind the Music 3rd Anniversary (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - "Nightclubbing" Save the Last Dance (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - "Shake Appeal" VH1 The List (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Rhino Punk box set (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - "Lust for Life" Donna's Top 200 Vol. 3 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - "Gimme Danger" Dogtown (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Iggy Poem "Fleas" The Crow (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Excite UK / UK Spot (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - The Crow Documentary, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Stereo Vision LA / Iggy paintings (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Horton Hospital / Nikki Synis (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - "Search and Destroy" Chili Peppers DVD (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - "China Girl" VH1 Storytellers (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Bug Statements, January to June 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bug Statements, July to December 2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "The Passenger" Saturn commercial (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Germany tour (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Real Wild Child" VH1 Best Buy (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "Death in Vegas" Gran Turismo (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Lust for Life" Modern Rock Vol. 18 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "Lust for Life" Ally McBeal (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "Dirt/Street" Spin Cycle Movie (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - "The Passenger" Adventures of Sebastian Cole (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Arista Heritage (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - KLM Magazine request (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "The Passenger" Freaks and Geeks (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - "The Passenger" Dr. Martens box set (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" EMI Korea (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "Lust for Life" VH1 1977 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "Avenue B" 20th Century Lullabies (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - "Candy" Picking Up the Pieces (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "Lust for Life" Pottpett Rock 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - "Nightclubbing" Shyne Sample (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - "Lust for Life" Ryan Caulfield TV (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - "Avenue B" Belgium compilation (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - "Lust for Life" Best Student Anthems (South Africa) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Reebok ad (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Alfa Romeo / EMI Publishing (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Now That's Vocal (Australia Virgin) (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - "Louie Louie" Motorrock (Virgin World) (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Funhouse box set (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - "Tonight" Tina Turner (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Marc Du Poniface / Space Goofs (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - "Gimme Danger" Dogtown (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "Lust for Life" WBTV Nikki (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1 Shocking Moments (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - "Down on the Streets" Knockaround Guys (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - "The Passenger" Rock Party (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Les Enfants du Rock (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Nude and Rude Two Pack / Virgin Europe (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - "Lust for Life" The Replacements (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - "The Passenger" British Airways (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - "Wild America" Platinum Rock 90's (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - "The Passenger" Club Makeup (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - "Lust for Life" Modern Rock Vol. 18 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Mandy Stein correspondence (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - "Penetration" Promo Synch (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - The Undefeated (Belgium CD) (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - "Lust for Life" Shockwave Corp. Video (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - "I Need More" Le Serpant A Plumes (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Casino (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Dan Rose correspondence (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Reebok Ad Prototype (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Dell Computer Sessions (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Jerry Saviola / Grey Advertising (Box 15, Folder 52)